

cameronway.net camerondway@gmail.com 812.272.4877

SMILLS

Web Technologies HTML

CSS

Scripts/UI JavaScript

jQuery

CSS Preprocessors

Stylus

JavaScript Libraries React

Version Control GIT

Content Management SystemsCraft

ExpressionEngine

Kentico

Accessibility Testing Tools

SiteSort

Design Tools Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Sketch

CAMERON WAY Web Developer

PROFILE

Proactive and motivated developer focused on Front-end accessible websites and applications that create high-quality user experiences for all users. With 5+ years of professional experience working with a wide array of clients and needs including sports and medical fields, using technology not limited to content management systems such as Craft, ExperssionEngine, along slide the latest web standards, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript ES6.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Developer (May 2017 - October 2018)

Jr. Developer (May 2014 - May 2017)

TrendyMinds

Indianapolis, Indiana

Working as a developer at TrendyMinds, alongside a small team of both Front-end and Back-end developers across the country to build user friendly websites by incorporating the latest industry standards.

My duties included:

- Building and testing modules for client sites.
- Creating hour estimates for implementing new features on client sites.
- Conducting browser quality assurance for entire websites and new features.
- Accessibility testing using SiteSort and the Axe browser extension, as well at manually testing pages and modules with Mac OS VoiceOver.

Front End Developer (October 2013 - May 2014)

USA Track & Field

Indianapolis, Indiana

My duties included:

- Working with the CMS, Kentico.
- Developing graphics for the web.
- Designing and developing different parts of the USATF site, as well as the many USATF association pages.
- Troubleshooting Issues within the CMS, as well as helping service our team and our many associations on the USA Track & Field Network.
- Working with the GreenSock Animation Platform to animate web pages.

EDUCATION

Bachelors of Science in Web Design and Interactive Media

The Art Institute of Indianapolis

Indianapolis, Indiana

October 2010 - September 2013